<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Kasun Buddhi</title>
    <link>https://kasunbuddhi.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kasun Buddhi</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://kasunbuddhi.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://kasunbuddhi.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:15:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kasunbuddhi.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Verification Environment of Peripherals for PULP RISC-V architecture using UVM</title>
      <link>https://kasunbuddhi.com/projects/verification_environment_pulp_riscv_architecture_uvm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kasunbuddhi.com/projects/verification_environment_pulp_riscv_architecture_uvm/</guid>
      <description>PULP is a RISC-V architecture which has peripherals interconnected with micro DMA system. This Verification Environment is designed to validate the peripherals with microDMA system with in the PULP platform. Presently, It has ability to verifying SPI and UART protocols, with plans to extends its capabilities to other peripherals in the future. Leveraging the UVM library, it facilitates the creation of reusable verification components and test environments using SystemVerilog.
Application We are concentrating on enhancing PULP uDMA system with peripherals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to the UVM</title>
      <link>https://kasunbuddhi.com/blogs/introduction-to-the-uvm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kasunbuddhi.com/blogs/introduction-to-the-uvm/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to the UVM When I was getting into UVM (Universal Verification Methodology) as my verification framework or methodology, I faced many difficulties. So I decided to make an article for beginners or intermediate people who do not have a clear picture of the UVM. I am not going to explain the history of UVM here. Because intermediate people are more like to know the theories other than the history lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AXI4S FIFO test unit</title>
      <link>https://kasunbuddhi.com/projects/axi4s-fifo-test-unit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kasunbuddhi.com/projects/axi4s-fifo-test-unit/</guid>
      <description>AXI4S FIFO test unit This will help to verify modules which contains AXI4-Stream ports. This is a project which I have done with Accelr team. The purpose of this VIP is to facilitate the verification process of RTL DUTs that utilize the AXI4-Stream protocol. By integrating our VIP, design and verification engineers gain the ability to customize packets that adhere to the AXI4-Stream protocol, enabling comprehensive testing of their designs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Cleaning Robot for Domestic Environment - Simulation in Webots</title>
      <link>https://kasunbuddhi.com/projects/kasun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kasunbuddhi.com/projects/kasun/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Cleaning is the most common household task we perform in our everyday life. For kids ages 2 to 5, tidying up their room and vacuum cleaning the house is a challenging and tiring task that most people faced in their day-to-day life. This report presents our Final Year Project of Intelligent Floor Cleaning Robot that can perform Object arrangement and Tidy up tasks in the Kids’ Room and efficient cleaning tasks for the Living Room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://kasunbuddhi.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kasunbuddhi.com/about/</guid>
      <description>In my daytime, I work as a DV Engineer at a Sri Lankan Tech company.
At night, I&amp;rsquo;m a Open source contributor in Hardware and Software.
 💻 GitHub  You can also connect with me at the following social platforms:
 Twitter LinkedIn  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infographics</title>
      <link>https://kasunbuddhi.com/infographics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kasunbuddhi.com/infographics/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 1st post</title>
      <link>https://kasunbuddhi.com/page/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kasunbuddhi.com/page/</guid>
      <description>Desc Text.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
