<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Kasun Buddhi</title>
    <link>https://kasunbuddhi.com/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Kasun Buddhi</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://kasunbuddhi.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://kasunbuddhi.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 23:15:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kasunbuddhi.com/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to the UVM</title>
      <link>https://kasunbuddhi.com/blogs/introduction-to-the-uvm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kasunbuddhi.com/blogs/introduction-to-the-uvm/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to the UVM When I was getting into UVM (Universal Verification Methodology) as my verification framework or methodology, I faced many difficulties. So I decided to make an article for beginners or intermediate people who do not have a clear picture of the UVM. I am not going to explain the history of UVM here. Because intermediate people are more like to know the theories other than the history lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Bioinformatics</title>
      <link>https://kasunbuddhi.com/blogs/what-is-bioinformatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kasunbuddhi.com/blogs/what-is-bioinformatics/</guid>
      <description>Introduction So you probably have heard of the term Bioinformatics before, but did not get the chance to learn more about what it is and what it can do.
In this article, I will be giving you a brief high-level overview of this exciting field of Bioinformatics. Thus, the article will be comprehensible to those coming from biology or computer backgrounds alike.
As a biologist, I have self-taught myself data science and coding (R and Python) after several years of persistence (initially quitting a couple of times the coding concept just kind of clicked at some point in time).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
